import { Questions } from "./questions";

export const ITEMS: Questions[]= [

    {
        question:"The Movie is the story of Kamini, a vivacious and career conscious young lady who works in a TV channel. One morning, she finds herself lying completely naked in a deserted structure following a late-night party. Stark naked and having no phone to communicate, how she battles to get back safely and unlocks the mystery behind what happened that night makes up the rest of the film.",
        option1:"Ratsasan",
        option2:"Aame",
        option3:"Christopher",
        option4:"Mynaa",
        answer:"Aame",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Aame. 13 More to go!!",
        wrong:"Nah",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"Akash(Hero) is a practical and easy going young guy and he does not have a very good opinion about women and love stories. His friend Kittu (Vennela Kishore) is in a Facebook relationship with a girl named Lalli (Chinmayee Ghatrazu). When the time comes to meet each other, Kittu develops cold feet and out of a fear of rejection, sends in Akash to meet Lalli. On the other side, Lalli decides to send her friend Lavanya (Shanvi) to the meeting. It is love at first sight for this ‘new’ couple and very soon, they develop a deep bond. Just when everything seems rosy for the lovebirds, Lavanya's father Mangalampalli Maharadhi (Rajendra Prasad) enters the scene and is not impressed with Akash's behaviour. It is now up to Akash to convince Maharadhi to change his mind.",
        option1:"Next Nuvve",
        option2:"Jodi",
        option3:"Crazy Fellow",
        option4:"Lovely",
        answer:"Lovely",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Lovely. 12 More to go!!",
        wrong:"nah",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"Satya is an MBBS graduate, who relocates to Kurnool/Madurai with his mother as he gets a job as doctor in a government hospital in Kurnool. He meets RJ Mahalakshmi, who is popularly known as 'Whistle' Mahalakshmi, and soon develops feelings for her. He also learns about Guru, a ruthless gangster, who rules the city with an iron fist. Satya lodges a complaint against Guru, whose company has been manufacturing poisonous saline and is involved in the medical mafia Guru's wife Swarna plots to kill Satya by stringing, but instead, Mahalakshmi gets hurt by getting a major cut on her throat as she was following Satya. Satya admits her to the hospital, where he learns that she might not be able to speak again. He gets informed that Guru has been released from prison. After being encouraged by his mother, Satya calls Guru back to the Konda Reddy fort, for a final showdown. After close hand-to-hand combat, Satya kills Guru and hangs him, in the same manner, that Guru hanged him before. After Guru/'s death, Satya gets married to Maha, where he continues working as a doctor and a police officer.",
        option1:"Pokiri",
        option2:"Naa Peru Surya, Naa Illu India",
        option3:"Warriorr",
        option4:"Race Gurram",
        answer:"Warriorr",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Warriorr. 11 More to go!!",
        wrong:"nah",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"In 1991, Gautham a wealthy man sees Mithuna for the first time and falls in love with her. However she becomes involved in an accident and is on her death bed. Gautham pays for her surgeries and she recovers but after she gains consciousness, Mithuna asks about Surya. Apparently, both are in love with each other but Mithuna is told that Surya is dead. Meanwhile, Gautham expresses his feelings and he takes her to Ooty and shows his love for Mithuna, who is unable to forget Surya. The two often fight and argue and one day Mithuna goes missing. Gautham thinks that Mithuna has left the house to commit suicide. He slaps her but realizes that she accepts his love and has decided to marry him. As he goes to Hyderabad to make the arrangements for the wedding, he suddenly sees a painting of Mithuna on the road. A beggar tells him that a mad man named Surya drew it, which shocks Gautham. The beggar tells him that Surya stays near a factory and to his disbelief, he finds glass bottles of different colors arranged to represent Mithuna's face. Surya is revealed to be alive and is distraught at the thought of Mithuna being dead.",
        option1:"Andhala Rakshashi",
        option2:"Tuneega Tuneega",
        option3:"Soggade Chinni Nayana",
        option4:"Baana Kaathadi",
        answer:"Andhala Rakshashi",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Andhala Rakshashi. 10 More to go!!",
        wrong:"nah",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"Renu (Swasika) loses her golden ear pendant. She searches for it and in the process finds love, in the form of Hari (Sai Krishna), an engineering student.",
        option1:"Hello",
        option2:"Yetu Choosina Nuvve",
        option3:"Mr. Majnu",
        option4:"Tuneega Tuneega",
        answer:"Yetu Choosina Nuvve",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Yetu Choosina Nuvve. 9 More to go!!",
        wrong:"I dont blame you for choosing the wrong answer, this movie is not that popular",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"A village girl with a disturbing past comes to live in the city without money and is helped by a man. He encourages her to start modeling and turns her into a popular actor and model. He starts falling for her but her past prevents their future.",
        option1:"Sitara",
        option2:"Tamacha",
        option3:"Aalaapana",
        option4:"Amaran",
        answer:"Sitara",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Sitara. 8 More to go!!",
        wrong:"I brought up topic about this movie yesterday only lol.",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"Vinod, who has grown up under the care of a church father, is an introvert but a genius. He is forcibly sent to a college in Vizag by the father but is a complete misfit in class. Though shunned by the rest of his class, Divya becomes his friend and he gradually warms up to her. His feelings soon turn into love but he realizes that Divya considers him as only a friend. However, he is unwilling to let her go. Meanwhile, Vinod learns that Divya is in love with another classmate, Aadi.Vinod has set up a secret place in that jungle for executing his plan of wooing Divya. He makes her stay with him, while convincing her by talking about the unimpending arrival of Aadi. On one such day, he reveals his miserable past. While Divya clutches a tree bark tightly, Vinod and Aadi slip out and barely manage to hold either of her hands. Divya is forced to choose between her boyfriend and friend. Aadi's pleas notwithstanding, Divya doesn't have the heart to kill Vinod. Finally, Vinod decides to sacrifice himself and lets go of Divya's hand, falling to his death.",
        option1:"Nuvva Nena",
        option2:"Naandhi",
        option3:"Gamyam",
        option4:"Nenu",
        answer:"Nenu",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Nenu. 7 More to go!!",
        wrong:"nah",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"Varun is a non-resident Indian who lives in Austin, Texas, United States with his elder brother Raju and adopted, younger brother Bujji. He is a medical student aiming to become a neurosurgeon. Varun comes to India along with his younger brother for Raju's marriage to Renuka, whose family hails from Banswada in Telangana. There he meets Bhanumathi, Renuka's younger sister. Bhanu is a beautiful and confident girl who doesn't want to feel secondary to anyone. Gradually Varun and Bhanu develop a liking for each other but don't express it. Bhanu loves her father very dearly and doesn't believe in leaving him after her marriage.",
        option1:"Govindudu Andarivadele",
        option2:"Fidaa",
        option3:"Subramanyam for Sale",
        option4:"Orange",
        answer:"Fidaa",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Fidaa. 6 More to go!!",
        wrong:"Idhi etla Wrong guess chesinave thingarii!!!",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"(Popular Hindi movie, later the remake was done in Telugu with your Fav hero). When an earthquake destroys an atheist Kanji's antique shop, he decides to sue God. However, when Lord Krishna helps him fight the lawsuit and expose the corrupt charlatans, his faith is restored.",
        option1:"Oh my god",
        option2:"Oh Baby",
        option3:"Sahasam",
        option4:"Gopala Gopala",
        answer:"Oh my god",
        correct:"Oh my god!! Thats right, it is Oh my god. 5 More to go!!",
        wrong:"Hindi Movie ani clearly mentioned kadha..thingari...",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"(This's Hero's first movie) Raj is a Hyderabad-based gambler living with his adopted parents who support his means of living. Tragedy strikes the family when his adopted father is diagnosed with cirrhosis as a result of alcoholism. Raj needs ₹20 lakhs for his father's liver transplantation, which must be done within a month. As he is on the lookout for money, he is approached by James, his rival in betting, with a betting challenge. James dares Raj to make Chaitra, a dental student and the daughter of a dreaded and influential businessman Bellary, fall in love with him. If he is able to complete the task before 31 December 2011, James will give him the money needed for his father's operation; if not, he has to give up betting forever. Desperate for the money, Raj takes up the challenge and begins wooing Chaitra. Chaitra soon reciprocates his advances. Bellary finds out about their relationship and sends his henchmen to kill the couple on the night of 31 December. Raj and Chaitra successfully dodge the henchmen and escape to Srisailam. ",
        option1:"Chirutha",
        option2:"Devadas",
        option3:"Racha",
        option4:"Gambler",
        answer:"Racha",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Racha. 4 More to go!!",
        wrong:"nah",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"Karthik (Hero), an engineering graduate and an aspiring filmmaker falls instantly for Jessie (Heroine), a Malayali girl who is a year older to him and has a hard time wooing her. While Jessie is on the verge of admitting her liking towards him, her brother comes to know about Karthik and a quarrel takes place between their families. The Movie shows their various stages in love.",
        option1:"Snehitudau",
        option2:"Ride",
        option3:"Bheemili Kabaddi Jattu",
        option4:"Em Maya chesave",
        answer:"Em Maya chesave",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Em Maya chesave. 3 More to go!!",
        wrong:"Ever Green Movie, its First movie for both Hero and Heroine",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"As his roommates commit suicide one after another, an art college student tries to find the reasons behind them with help from a documentary filmmaker. The story revolves around the relativity between the history and the continuing suicides and how Magizh and jasmine untie the knots. This telugu movie is a romantic movie directed by Lawrence Dasari. Sourya, Sarayu and Parul Gulati appears in the lead roles.",
        option1:"Maya",
        option2:"Vanam",
        option3:"Demonte Colony",
        option4:"Ghost Stories",
        answer:"Vanam",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Vanam. 2 More to go!!",
        wrong:"nah",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"This telugu movie is a romantic movie directed by Lawrence Dasari. Sourya, Sarayu and Parul Gulati appears in the lead roles.",
        option1:"Enduko Nachav",
        option2:"Jadoogadu",
        option3:"Oka Manasu",
        option4:"Jyo Achyutananda",
        answer:"Enduko Nachav",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Enduko Nachav. 1 More to go!!",
        wrong:"nah",
        result: false
    },
    {
        question:"A simple family shifts into a new house where they begin to experience the presence of supernatural elements and attempt to get rid of the ghost residing in their humble abode.",
        option1:"Next Nuvve",
        option2:"Rakshasi",
        option3:"Ekkadiki Pothavu Chinnavada",
        option4:"Chandramukhi",
        answer:"Rakshasi",
        correct:"Thats right, it is Rakshasi. Well Done!! You successfully completed the quiz",
        wrong:"nah",
        result: false
    },
]